I don't know.
How could that possibly be?
It's a sword, but it's got to be at least 300 years old.
I think you're right.
It is. This is crazy. What should we do?
Is your heart about to beat out of your chest too?
Yeah.
Mr. Tanjiro, you came here because you need a new sword, right?
If that's the case, then it only makes sense you take this one.
No, no, no, no, no. That wouldn't be right.
The steel they used in the Sengoku period is the best quality ever.
No, no, I couldn't.
But the only reason we found it is because you broke it.
That's just because it took damage for 300 years.
And I just so happened to be there training with it when it finally broke.
Are you sure you don't want it?
How about we pull it out just to take a look?
I thought you'd never ask. Let's do it.
It's rusty.
Oh, yeah. I guess that makes sense, huh?
It has been neglected for the last 300 years, hasn't it?
Sorry I got us both worked up for nothing.
That's okay. I don't mind at all.
Whoa! Please don't cry, Mr. Tanjiro! I'm sorry!
What's that?
Sorry.
Who's that?
Thank you.
Mr. Hageneska?
No need to explain.
I heard everything.
Allow me to take it from here.
Take what from here?
What do you think you're doing?
Just leave it to me.
Please let go of it.
And why are you trying to take off with it anyway?
Quit asking questions and leave it to me.
You can't just show up out of the blue and say leave it to me.
That doesn't make sense.
You just leave it to me.
Not a chance.
This belongs to Goten Tzu.
Just leave it to me.
You know, I came all the way here to see you.
Where have you been hiding?
Leave it to me means leave it to me.
I asked you what you meant by that because we have no idea what the heck you're talking about.
What part of leave it to me, don't you two understand?
What kind of grown-up acts like that?
Pay attention, boys.
Mr. Hageneska's weak spots are his sides.
All you've got to do is this.
Tickle me.
Hey, Mr. Kanamori.
Long time no see.
Hey, long time no see, Tanjiro.
Mr. Hageneska always goes limp for a while after being tickled.
So I'll do the explaining for him.
Please try your best to forgive Mr. Hageneska.
You see, he's been hiding out in the mountains, training.
Training?
That's right.
All in order to forge you a stronger sword so that you won't be killed in battle.
But he'd never admit that himself.
He did that for me?
All this time, you've been asking Mr. Hageneska for another sword, right?
I'm sure it made him very happy.
After all, he's always losing clients because most swordsmen can't stand him.
I never would have guessed.
This guy's got about the worst social skills I've ever seen.
It's no wonder he still can't find himself a bride.
Oh, look, he's been revived.
I shall take this ancient rusty sword into my care.
And by using the Nichirin sword polishing art of the Hageneska family,
I will surely be able to restore it.
Why didn't you just say all that from the start, you big dummy?
Instead of repeating, leave it to me like some kind of maniac.
Well, guess that's expecting too much.
What the hell just came out of your mouth?
I dare you to say that again!
I can't breathe!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
His sides! His sides! Quick, go for his sides!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
I'll be taking this sword with me.
This one should hold you over while I work on it.
Thank you very much!
So, yeah, that's what happened yesterday, see?
They say it takes three days and three nights to properly polish a sword.
So he'll be finished the day after tomorrow.
I'm worried, though.
They say that polishing art of his is so brutal that some have died doing it.
I know he strictly forbade me from checking in on him.
But maybe I should, right?
I don't know! And I don't care!
Now stop talking to me like we're friends or something!
Huh? Hold on, you mean we're not friends?
Not by a long shot, idiot!
Do I have to remind you that you broke my arm?
Don't tell me you've already forgotten.
I remember it being your own fault because you hit a girl, Genya.
I had no choice.
Don't ever call me by my first name!
These rice crackers are tasty. Want one?
Damn you! Now I don't want one! Get lost!
Wait, that's odd. Didn't you lose a front tooth? Back at the hot spring?
Uh...
You must have been seeing things.
Not only did I see it, but I've still got it.
You kept it in your pocket?
What kind of creep does something like that?
But you dropped it, so I thought I'd return it to you.
Have you got soft in the head? Get rid of that thing!
Now scream!
Like this, like that, and then something like this.
Then I go like this, I think.
I wonder why Genya's in a bad mood all the time.
Could it be that he's just hungry and that's why?
Hey, I know. We should ask him to have breakfast.
You think it's a good idea, too?
We already soaked in the hot spring, so I'm sure he'd say yes.
I like Genya. I'd like to get closer to him.
Man, braiding sure is difficult.
But look, now you've got the same hairstyle as Ms. Konrochi.
Hey, Nezuko. Doesn't the moon look beautiful tonight?
I might have soaked a little too long tonight.
I gotta get to bed for my early shift tomorrow.
Hmm?
A face?
I don't remember seeing anything like that on the way up.
Who put this here?
Someone could trip on this and get hurt.
Don't you?
Are you okay?
No, no, no!
Thank you.
I don't know.
I can't lift up.
Go to the light.
Get out of here.
$500.
How will you do that?
Anyаты?
Maybe I will interest you.
How will you get it to him?
Maybe I will do that.
I will take it all the time to scene,
how horrible how horrible i suppose i should have known that a mountain swordsmith's flesh
would be unfit for my consumption but that's what makes it so appealing
if i can destroy this place then those demon slayers
will be without a place to craft their precious swords i must try to move quickly i must try to
move quickly thanks to gyoko we were able to locate their hidden village
but that doesn't change the fact that my lord is angry quickly quickly
we must kill every one of them anyone who opposes my lord must be eliminated
old man you done you're not here
brother
i have no choice but to do this
have you seen the swordsmith named kanamori
oh hey tokito is something wrong wait hold on a second did you just pinch my nose
yes i did and you took far too long to react no no i would have sensed it if there were any animosity
yes but would you pinch someone's nose with animosity sure i know mr kanamori what's wrong if i had to
guess he's with mr haganeska kanamori's been appointed to be my new swordsmith so where's haganeska then
i don't know let's go look
why do you care so much about other people isn't there something you'd rather do for yourself right now
life has a way of rewarding good deeds oftentimes when you help others you're helping yourself
i was planning to go anyway so why not huh huh hold on repeat what you just said say it say it huh
that i was planning to go anyway i'm glad to see her awake nezuko that hurt
let's go see mr haganeska
this girl is certainly an odd creature isn't she what what do you mean well i just get this feeling
let's see how do i explain i get the feeling that i've met this girl before was she like this when i
met her how should i put it is someone else here it seems like it
what is that is it a demon what is a demon doing here i didn't notice him until i saw him
there's no doubt this demon's an upper rank
mist breathing fourth form shifting flow slash
he's quick i couldn't take him out please stop it please stop tormenting me
it hurts don't lose your nerve this demon is a mass murderer otherwise you wouldn't have been able
to dodge that attack inokami kagura sunflower thrust
did i get him why isn't he fighting back is he not upper rank
he decapitated him and so fast but upper ranks don't always die so easily even if you behead them
up for further
tokito stay focused
he split him too one of them grew ahead while the other grew out of body
He split in two
One of them grew a head
While the other grew out of body
I'll take this one
If we can strike them simultaneously
Nezuko
Tokito
Hey now, this is pretty fun
Did you see how far that pipsqueak went flying?
Did you, Sekiro?
There's nothing fun about this
All I'm feeling is uncontrollable rage
Karaku
I despise being lumped in with you
Oh, is that right?
Well, good thing we got separated then
Again?
Are we going to have to behead two of them at once again?
What is this?
It must be that stab
This is bad
I'm about to lose consciousness
Someone's on the
On the roof
Genya
What is that?
A gun?
If it is, why does it have the same scent as a Nichiren sword?
I must have missed one of them
This is even more fun and entertaining than I thought
I've never been hit with an attack that felt like that
Can you wait?
No matter what you do, this demon
Can't be killed
It'll only end up multiplying
It gets younger and stronger
They're counting on us beheading them
It's like this demon doesn't care about being decapitated
Meaning its vital spot is in its head
It's splitting into four and regenerating
Is there a pattern?
Which part heals up first?
It has to have some kind of weakness
Find it
Figure it out
What is it?
I thought it split up into four demons
This makes my heart sing
It's been so long since I was last split off
This demon can fly
All four of them must have different powers
Nezuko, forget about me
Try and help Genya
You're so weak, it's almost sad, really
Genya!
Nezuko, save him!
You have to try and save Genya, hurry!
You must be pretty confident to be worrying about someone else right now
Kino Kami Kagura!
Not bad
This is turning out to be quite the delight
Crap onto a branch
A branch!
Get up right now
Get on your feet
The villagers are in danger
I have to protect them
Dammit
My body's gone numb
I can't hear anything either
I got blasted quite a distance
I've got to get back quickly
A demon and a child
Unfortunately, as a swordsmith
The child is still unseasoned
Therefore saving him is a low priority
Judging by its presence
That's not the main body
But something generated by a spell
There's no reason to stop and fight it now
If the entire village is under attack
Then the village chief comes first
Those with greater skills and talents
Are my top priority to protect
My objective is to annihilate that upper-ranked demon
And protect the village at all costs
Saving an inexperienced budding swordsmith
Won't amount to any
Life is a way of rewarding good deeds
Often when you help others
You're helping yourself
Run
It's you
Run for it before you get in my way even more
I got the element ii
but evenelf
You remember that
You've always been doing my same tag
I go the element ii
No, you can't find there
There's always a work
You walked
You weren't using day
You were using mañana
I don't think it's fair deal
Transcrição e Legendas por Quintena Coelho
A demon showed up while Mr. Hageneska was off working on your sword.
But are you alright?
Thankfully, Mr. Hageneska forged this for me.
It's good to see Mr. Hageneska hasn't changed.
If he did, it wouldn't be for the better.
Now it's time for a Taisho-era secret.
Mr. Hageneska has wind chimes on his umbrella because he really likes wind chimes.
And when he was little, every time he threw a tantrum,
the grown-ups around him would play wind chimes to try and quiet him down.
Wow, I didn't know that.
This is for you, Mr. Tanjiro.
If you think something like a wind chime will put me in a better mood,
you couldn't be more wrong!
Wind chime, chime, chime!
Stop treating me like a child!
Chime, chime, chime!
Up next, episode four.
Thank you, Tokito.
Have you calmed down now?
I said I'm not a child!
Chime, chime, chime!